Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine UP028
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine
1899 -- 2022
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Dental Medicine
UP028
0.5 Linear Feet
7 Volumes
33 Digital Object(s)
10.74 Megabytes Of the 33 digital objects in this series, 20 have extent information comprising 10.74 MB.
This collection contains the course Bulletin for the Tufts School of Dental Medicine from 1899 -- 2022.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized chronologically in one series.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University School of Dental Medicine was established in 1868 as Boston Dental College. It was incorporated into Tufts College in 1899. Although founded as a school to educate students from New England, today Tufts is renowned throughout the United States and the world as a center for academic and clinical excellence. Tufts boasts over 6,900 alumni composed of individuals from all fifty states and thirty-nine countries. The majority of the alumni outside of the USA have completed an Advanced Education Certificate program. Students receive a comprehensive education emphasizing the importance of didactic coursework, clinical experience, and practice management that prepares them to enter the work force as confident, proficient clinicians.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the course Bulletin for the Tufts School of Dental Medicine. There is a gap between the book published during the 1979/80 year and the 1988/89 year.
- Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1899 -- 2022; 1899 -- 1980; UP028.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 7 Volumes; 33 Digital Object(s); 10.74 Megabytes Of the 33 digital objects in this series, 20 have extent information comprising 10.74 MB.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of the course Bulletins for the Tufts School of Dental Medicine. There is a gap between the book published during the 1979/80 year and the 1988/89 year.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Physical condition. Open for research.
  - Tufts College Dental School, Catalogue 1899-1900 Announcement 1900-01, 1899 -- 1901; UP028.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
    Open for research.
  - Tufts College Dental School, Catalogue 1900-01 Announcement 1901-02, 1900 -- 1902; UP028.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School, Catalogue 1901-02 Announcement 1902-03, 1901 -- 1903; UP028.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School, Catalogue 1902-03 Announcement 1903-04, 1902 -- 1904; UP028.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School, Catalogue 1903-04 Announcement 1904-05, 1903 -- 1905; UP028.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School, Catalogue 1904-05 Announcement 1905-06, 1904 -- 1906; UP028.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School, Catalogue 1905-06 Announcement 1906-07, 1905 -- 1907; UP028.001.001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School Catalogue, 1906 -- 1907; UP028.001.001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School Catalogue, 1907 -- 1908; UP028.001.001.00009 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School Catalogue, 1908 -- 1909; UP028.001.001.00010 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School Catalogue, 1909 -- 1910; UP028.001.001.00011 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School Catalogue, 1910 -- 1911; UP028.001.001.00012 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School Catalogue, 1911 -- 1912; UP028.001.001.00013 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School Catalogue, 1912 -- 1913; UP028.001.001.00014 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Dental School Catalogue, 1913 -- 1914; UP028.001.001.00015 (Box Volume 1)
  - Catalogue of the Dental School, 1910 -- 1911; UP028.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
  - Catalogue of the Dental School, 1911 -- 1912; UP028.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
  - Catalogue of the Dental School, 1912 -- 1913; UP028.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
  - Catalogue of the Dental School, 1913 -- 1914; UP028.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)
  - Requirements for admission to the Dental School, 1914-03; UP028.001.002.00005 (Box Volume 2)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1915 -- 1916; UP028.001.002.00006 (Box Volume 2)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1916 -- 1917; UP028.001.002.00007 (Box Volume 2)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1917 -- 1918; UP028.001.002.00008 (Box Volume 2)
    Physical condition.
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1918 -- 1919; UP028.001.002.00009 (Box Volume 2)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1919 -- 1920; UP028.001.002.00010 (Box Volume 2)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1920 -- 1921; UP028.001.003.00001 (Box Volume 3)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1921 -- 1922; UP028.001.003.00002 (Box Volume 3)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1922 -- 1923; UP028.001.003.00003 (Box Volume 3)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1923 -- 1924; UP028.001.003.00004 (Box Volume 3)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1924 -- 1925; UP028.001.003.00005 (Box Volume 3)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1925 -- 1926; UP028.001.003.00006 (Box Volume 3)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1926 -- 1927; UP028.001.003.00007 (Box Volume 3)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1927 -- 1928; UP028.001.003.00008 (Box Volume 3)
  - Announcement of the Dental School, 1928 -- 1929; UP028.001.003.00009 (Box Volume 3)
  - Dental School number, 1929 -- 1930; UP028.001.004.00001 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1930 -- 1931; UP028.001.004.00002 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1931 -- 1932; UP028.001.004.00003 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1932-03; UP028.001.004.00004 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1933-05; UP028.001.004.00005 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1934-02; UP028.001.004.00006 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1935-01; UP028.001.004.00007 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1936-02; UP028.001.004.00008 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1937-01; UP028.001.004.00009 (Box Volume 4)
  - Dental School number, 1938-01; UP028.001.005.00001 (Box Volume 5)
  - Dental School number, 1939-02; UP028.001.005.00002 (Box Volume 5)
  - Dental School number, 1940-02; UP028.001.005.00003 (Box Volume 5)
  - Dental School number, 1941-01; UP028.001.005.00004 (Box Volume 5)
  - Dental School number, 1942-01; UP028.001.005.00005 (Box Volume 5)
  - Dental School number, 1943-11; UP028.001.005.00006 (Box Volume 5)
  - Dental School number, 1945-12; UP028.001.006.00001 (Box Volume 6)
  - Dental School number, 1946-12; UP028.001.006.00002 (Box Volume 6)
  - Dental School number, 1947-12; UP028.001.006.00003 (Box Volume 6)
  - Dental School number, 1948-12; UP028.001.006.00004 (Box Volume 6)
  - Dental School number, 1949-12; UP028.001.006.00005 (Box Volume 6)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1961; UP028.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1961 -- 1962; UP028.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1962 -- 1963; UP028.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1963 -- 1964; UP028.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1964 -- 1965; UP028.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1965 -- 1966; UP028.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1966 -- 1967; UP028.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1969 -- 1970; UP028.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1970 -- 1971; UP028.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1971 -- 1972; UP028.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1972 -- 1973; UP028.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1973 -- 1974; UP028.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1974 -- 1975; UP028.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1975 -- 1977; UP028.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1978 -- 1979; UP028.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1979 -- 1980; UP028.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1983 -- 1984; UP028.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1984 -- 1985; UP028.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1986 -- 1987; UP028.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1987 -- 1988; UP028.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1990 -- 1991; UP028.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College Dental School Number, 1951 -- 1952; UP028.001.008.00001 (Box Volume 8)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2013; UP028.001.00001
    Fall 2013 course bulletin for School of Dental Medicine
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2014; UP028.001.00002
    Spring 2014 course bulletin for School of Dental Medicine
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2014; UP028.001.00003
    Fall 2014 course bulletin for School of Dental Medicine
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2014; UP028.001.00004
    Fall 2014 course bulletin for Dental Advanced Education
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2015; UP028.001.00005
    Spring 2015 course bulletin for Dental Advanced Education
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2015; UP028.001.00006
    Fall 2015 course bulletin for School of Dental Medicine
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2015; UP028.001.00007
    Fall 2015 course bulletin for Dental Advanced Education
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2016; UP028.001.00008
    Spring 2016 course bulletin for School of Dental Medicine
  - Bulletin of Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2016; UP028.001.00009
    Spring 2016 course bulletin for Dental Advanced Education
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2016; UP028.001.00010; School of Dental Medicine; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.5 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2016
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2016, accession 2017.022.
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2016; UP028.001.00011; School of Dental Medicine; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.19 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2016
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2017; UP028.001.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.2 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2017
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2017, accession UP-2018-012.
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2017; UP028.001.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.59 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2017
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2017; UP028.001.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.64 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2017
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2017; UP028.001.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.2 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2017
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2018; UP028.001.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.2 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2018
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2018, accession UP-2018-033.
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2018; UP028.001.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.4 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2018
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2018; UP028.001.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.2 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2018
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2018; UP028.001.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.42 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2018
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2019; UP028.001.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.26 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2019
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2019; UP028.001.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.7 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2019
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2019; UP028.000100
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2019; UP028.000101
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2020; UP028.000102
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2020; UP028.000103
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2020; UP028.000104; 849 Kilobytes
    School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2020
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2020; UP028.000105; 1.4 Megabytes
    School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2020
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2021; UP028.000106; 849.76 Kilobytes
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2021; UP028.000107; 1.45 Megabytes
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2021; UP028.000108; 836.17 Kilobytes
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2021; UP028.000109; 1.45 Megabytes
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Spring 2022; UP028.000112; 1 Digital Object(s); 277 Kilobytes
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Spring 2022; UP028.000113; 1 Digital Object(s); 551 Kilobytes
  - School of Dental Medicine Bulletin, Fall 2022; UP028.000111; 1 Digital Object(s); 278 Kilobytes
  - School of Dental Medicine, Postgraduate Bulletin, Fall 2022; UP028.000114; 1 Digital Object(s); 570 Kilobytes